你在第一课的学习中已经完成了许多。
You accomplished a lot in this first lesson. Starting with nothing more
从一腔热血手持Android Studio开始学习，你已经创建了你的第一个工程。
than Android Studio and hope, you've created your first project. Built and
在虚拟设备和物理设备上生成和配置程序，
deployed it to virtual and actual devices, and
并在UI上创建一个简单的列表使用适配器填充。
even created a simple list-based UI that's populated using an adapter.
你也学习到一点关于移动端和android端开发，尤其是，
You also learned a little about what makes mobile and Android, in particular,
在不同的环境下开发，像桌面、网页和服务端。
a different environment to develop for the desktop, web, and server. But we've
这只是刚刚开始。我们的应用程序到现在为止使用的还是静态模拟数据。
only just gotten started. The app we've got so far is using static mock data.
所以，我们将会在第二课里继续学习，如何得到真正的天气数据。
So join us in lesson two to learn how to hook it up to real weather data.
那么在这之前，花点时间拓展一下你的认知，
But before that, take a moment to cleanse your palate with
关于Android生态系统的历史和演变。
a brief interlude exploring the history and evolution of the Android ecosystem.